Guide to the Treasurer, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1717-1940; Series III
  - Filing Code
    - 173. Police, Campus, 1907 March-1932 November (Box 308, Folder 1939)
    - 175. Lampson Lyceum, 1907-1919 (Box 308, Folder 1940)
    - 176. Royalties on Hymns, 1911 March (Box 309, Folder 1941)
    - 177. Telephones, 1907-1929 (Box 309, Folder 1942-1944)
    - 178. Budget, 1890s-1923 (Box 309, Folder 1945-1947)
    - 178. Budget, 1924-1929 (Box 310, Folder 1948-1952)
    - 179. Police: extra, 1907 May (Box 310, Folder 1953)
    - 180. City Bank of New Haven, 1914 September-October (Box 310, Folder 1954)
    - 181. Cartage, 1905-1910 (Box 310, Folder 1955)
    - 182. Class Records, 1907 April (Box 310, Folder 1956)
    - 183. Hendrie Fund, 1907 April (Box 310, Folder 1957)
    - 184. Tuition Abatements, 1907 April-1914 October (Box 310, Folder 1958)
    - 185. Suspense Account: Yale Dining Club, 1906 September-1907 January (Box 310, Folder 1959)
    - 186. Wurts" Lawbooks: sale of, 1907 March-1908 April (Box 310, Folder 1960)
    - 187. American Mathematical Society Accounts, 1907 February-1909 April (Box 310, Folder 1961)
    - 188. Architecture Department, 1907, 1914, 1932, 1940 (Box 310, Folder 1962)
    - 188a. Architects: Rogers, James Gamble, 1914 June (Box 310, Folder 1963)
      See also: box 340, folder 2270
    - 188b. Architect, Consulting, 1908-1913 (Box 310, Folder 1964)
    - 188b. Architect, Consulting, 1914-1917 (Box 311, Folder 1965)
    - 189. Aid for Students, 1907, 1909, 1917 (Box 311, Folder 1966)
    - 190. Parks (W. H.): will, 1907 February (Box 311, Folder 1967)
    - 191. Coal: Peabody Coal Co., 1907 February (Box 311, Folder 1968)
    - 192. Commencement, 1907-1928 (Box 311, Folder 1969-1970)
    - 192a. Class Secretaries Bureau and Clerical Bureau, 1917 January-1925 November (Box 311, Folder 1971)
    - 193. Day (George E.) Estate, 1907 June-1911 March (Box 311, Folder 1972)
    - 193a. 125 College St., 1909 June-October (Box 311, Folder 1973)
    - 194. Bromley Lectures, 1907-1913 (Box 311, Folder 1974)
    - 197. Long (Mahlon) Fund, 1948 April (Box 311, Folder 1975)
    - 198. Dana (James D.) Estate, 1907 April (Box 311, Folder 1976)
    - 200. Dodge Lectures, 1917-1922 (Box 311, Folder 1977)
    - 201. Rooms, Students: applications for, 1923-1928 (Box 311, Folder 1978-1980)
    - 201. Rooms, Student: applications for, 1929 (Box 312, Folder 1981)
    - 202. University Theatre: Yale Dramatic Association, 1907-1922 (Box 312, Folder 1982-1983)
    - 203. Chapel Music, 1908 October-1916 November (Box 312, Folder 1984)
    - 204. Elihu Yale Portrait, 1930 May-1912 May (Box 312, Folder 1985)
    - 205. Montgomery Prize, 1907 July-1912 July (Box 312, Folder 1986)
    - 207. White (Andrew D.) Prize, 1907 July-1916 May (Box 312, Folder 1987)
    - 208. Whitney (John A.) Annuity, 1906-1916 (Box 312, Folder 1988)
    - 209. Law School Library, 1908-1922 (Box 312, Folder 1989)
    - 210. Middlebury College, 1907 May-June (Box 312, Folder 1990)
    - 211. Bicentennial Publications, Yale, 1900 July-1917 May (Box 312, Folder 1991)
    - 212. Swimming Association, Yale, 1907 April-1908 April (Box 312, Folder 1992)
    - 213. Football Games: publicity, 1925 November (Box 312, Folder 1993)
    - 214. Advertising, 1907 June-1911 August (Box 312, Folder 1994)
    - 215. New Haven Railroad: claims against, 1906 November-1907 June (Box 312, Folder 1995)
    - 216. Flag Day, 1907 June (Box 312, Folder 1996)
    - 217. Tuition Rebates, 1905 February-1923 December (Box 312, Folder 1997)
    - 219. Law School: lighting, 1907 January-1909 January (Box 312, Folder 1998)
    - 220. Ridgefield School, 1907 June (Box 312, Folder 1999)
    - 221. Training Table, 1906 April-1914 October (Box 313, Folder 2000)
    - 222. Boathouse Property, 1909 April-1912 January (Box 313, Folder 2001)
    - 224. Peruvian Expedition: contributions to and Philip A. Means, Edwin A. Meserve, Meserve and Means, 1907-1909 (Box 313, Folder 2002)
    - 224. Peruvian Expedition: contributions to, 1911-1915 (Box 313, Folder 2003-2004)
    - 224. Peruvian Expedition: contributions to and Dr. Eaton'sreport, O. F. Cook account, Edwin L. Anderson, 1916 (Box 313, Folder 2005)
    - 224a. Peruvian Expedition: staff, 1914-1916 (Box 313, Folder 2006)
    - 226. Statements of Funds: received and invested, 1906-1912 (Box 313, Folder 2007)
    - 228. Land at Gales Ferry, Connecticut, 1907 March-April (Box 313, Folder 2008)
    - 229. Cook Prize, 1907 September-1911 June (Box 313, Folder 2009)
    - 230. Charles Washburn Clark, 1907 February-June (Box 313, Folder 2010)
    - 231. Law School: courses for academic students, 1906 July-1914 October (Box 313, Folder 2011)
    - 232. Boardman (Lucy H.) Estate, 1907 September-1910 March (Box 313, Folder 2012)
    - 233a. Geology, Summer School of, 1911 August-1916 October (Box 313, Folder 2013)
    - 233b. Geological Club deposits, 1911 December-1912 January (Box 313, Folder 2014)
    - 235. Water, 1907 April-1915 March (Box 313, Folder 2015)
    - 236. Real estate: New Haven, 1909 December-1912 October (Box 314, Folder 2016)
    - 237. Legal matters, 1907-1932 (Box 314, Folder 2017)
    - 238. Estates: (Box 314, Folder 2018-2022)
      Allen, Frank D.
      Anderson, Eunice M.
      Andrews, William Loring
      Angell, Joel H.
      Archibald, Julia A.
      Arnot, Matthias
      Bacon, Francis L.
      Baldwin, Simeon E.
      Barge, Benjamin F.
      Barnes, Jonathan
      Bayley, Norman B.
      Bedell, Emmeline Reed
      Beebe, Maria Louise
      Belden, E. B.
      Betts, C. Wyllis
      Bishop, Louis B.
      Bissell, Josiah H.
      Bliss, George T.
      Bliss, Philip N. and Nichols, Starr Hoyt
      Borden, M. C. D.
      Bowers, Edward A.
    - 238. Estates: (Box 315, Folder 2023-2029)
      Bradley, Susan L.
      Brady, A. N.
      Brown, Henry Billings
      Brown, Robert
      Butler, John Haskell
      Byers, Martha F.
      Camp, Cornelia E.
      Campbell, James E.
      Carpenter, Mary W.
      Carpenter, Zachary T.
      Chapin, C. H. B.
      Churchill, Lawrence W.
      Close, Francis H.
      Coit, Albert Merrill
      Cook, Professor
      Corning, Granville
      Cornwall, James H.
      Cory, Robert H.
      Cross, Harry P.
      Currier, Lura
      Curtis, John T.
      Curtis, T.W.T.
      Cutler, Francis E.
      Daily, Catherine
      Darr, Alice D.
      Day, Sherman
      DeForest, Robert W.
      Depew, Ganson
      Dexter, Morton
      Dexter, Stanley W.
    - 238. Estates: (Box 316, Folder 2030-2036)
      Dickinson, James T.
      Dimock, Otis K.
      Dodd, Frank C.
      Doneghy, Mrs. John T.
      Downes, John I. H.
      Dudley, Lucy B.
      Dudley, Plimmon H.
      Dutton, Samuel T.
      Duyckinck, W. C.
      Dwight, John W.
      Eagny, James T.
      Edwards, Amy R.
      Egleston, William C.
      Ehrich, Walter L.
      Elder, Samuel J.
      Ely, William D.
      Failing, John C.
      Farrel, Alton
      Farwell, Granger
      Fiske, Sarah J.
      Fitch, Lucius W.
      Fitch, Mary C. L.
      Fooks, Herbert C.
      Ford, David K.
      Frazier, Clara Duff
      Fuller, Egbert C.
      Gartland, George E.
      Gaylord, Thomas F.
      Gillet, Lorenzo
      Good, Mrs. Rosalia M.
      Goodell, J. Harriet
      Graham, Louise B.
      Griffin, William V.
      Grinnell, Morton
      Grinnell, William M.
      Hallgarten, Julius
      Harkness, Charles W.
      Harkness, Mary Warden
      Harkness, Mrs. Stephen V.
    - 238. Estates: (Box 317, Folder 2037-2042)
      Harriot, Mary A.
      Harris, Charles E.
      Hawes, James Anderson
      Hefflon, George Henry
      Hendrick, Mrs. Ellwood
      Hewitt, Frederick C.
      Heyworth, James O.
      Hicks, Ratcliffe
      Higbie, Hamilton A.
      Holmes, Edmund W.
      Hollister, Caroline Smith
      Hopkins, Albert A.
      Hotchkiss, Justus S.
      Hotchkiss, Marie Oakes
      Howe, Elmer P.
      Hoyt, Henry S.
      Ives, Brayton
      Ives, Mary E.
      Jackson, Isaac M.
      James, D. M.
      Jennings, Annie
      Judson, Robert M.
    - 238. Estates: (Box 318, Folder 2043-2047)
      Bridgeport and New Canaan Property
      The T. J. Pardy Construction Company
      Kellogg, Charles P.
      Kellogg, Louise W. B.
    - 238. Estates: (Box 319, Folder 2048-2052)
      Kennedy, John Stewart
      Kent, Albert E.
      Kittredge, George A.
      Kountze, Charles B.
      Lamb, Benjamin B.
      Lamson, William J., M.D.
      Lancraft, George E.
      Lane, Eva M. B.
      Lang, Benjamin J.
      Lathrop, John E.
      Lee, Emma B.
      Lewisohn, Walter
      Lines, Augustus E.
      Loudenslager, H. C.
      Lovejoy, Allen P.
      Lyman, Samuel H.
      Lynne, George S.
      McBride, Malcolm L.
      McClung, Robert G.
      McCrea, Mrs.
      McCully, Laura E.
      Macfarlane, Charles W.
      McLanahan, George X.
      McLane, Adelaide L.
      McLaughlin, Mary B.
      McLellen, Jessy
      McPherson, Edla J.
    - 238. Estates: (Box 320, Folder 2053-2057)
      Mallory, George W.
      Manners, John Hartley
      Mariani, Dr. Nicola
      Marquand, Frederick
      Marshall, James
      Martin, Mrs. Walter H.
      Masefield, John
      Maynard, Archibald B.
      Meara, Frank S.
      Menner, Robert J.
      Mercer, Alexander G.
      Merrill, Payson
      Merwin, Samuel E.
      Miscellaneous correspondence re bequests
      Monroe, Edwin D.
      Monroe, Virginia Marquand
      Morgan, Edwin D.
      Morgan, Terry V.
      Morse, Edward Lind
      Munson, C. S.
      Nichols, Effingham H.
      Niemeyer, Anna T.
      Osborn, Frederick W.
      Parker, Frank J.
      Parker, Frederick S.
      Parker, Joseph
      Payne, Oliver H.
      Peck, Eliza N.
      Peck, Tracy
      Penfield, Samuel L.
      Pennington, William
      Pratt, Francis C.
      Randall, Sands F.
      Raymond, Freeborn F.
      Reed, Edward M.
      Ripley, Alfred L.
      Robbins, Sarah Stuart
      Rogers, Samuel T.
      Roosa, DeWitt
      Ryerson, Edward L.
      Schlesinger, Frank
      Schramm, Arnold O.
      Schwab, John C.
      Scott, Mary Augusta
      Sedgwick, William T.
      Seesel, Albert
    - 238. Estates: (Box 321, Folder 2058-2062)
      Sheppard, Eustace Morrow
      Sherman, C. A.
      Shipley, Joseph L.
      Sill, Elizabeth
      Silliman, Augustus E.
      Silliman, Benjamin D.
      Slade, Charlotte Hill
      Smith, Charles Henry
      Smith, David P.
      Smith, Herbert Knox
      Smith, Loyal L.
      Southworth, Edward E.
      Southworth, Edward Wells
      Sprague, Albert Arnold
      Sprague, Nancy A.
      Staak, Dr. Herman
      Stanley, Katherine A.
      Stedman, Arthur
      Stedman, Edmund Clarence
      Sterling, Edward
      Sterling, John W.
      Stern, Henry Root
      Steward, Herbert
      Stimson, Lewis A.
      Stokes, Dr. Horace S.
      Styles, Flora N.
      Tarbell, Frank Bigelow
      Thorne, William V. S.
      Tompkins, Ray
      Townsend, Jane A.
      Townsend, Jane S.
    - 238. Estates: (Box 322, Folder 2063)
      Troesher, Robert
      Twiss, Julius
      Walker, Dr. D. A.
      Walker, E. A.
      Wellman, Guy
      Wells, Bradford
      Wendell, B. Rush
      Wheeler, Henry Lord
      White, Henry C.
      Wickham, Elizabeth M.
      Woodruff, Francis E.
      Wordin, Eliza Barnes
    - 238b. James (D. Willis): Estate (Box 322, Folder 2064)
    - Gifts: (Box 322, Folder 2065-2067)
      Bixby, W. K.
      Buckhout, Edward W.
      Cheney, Howell
      Dahl, George
      Dimock, Rev. E.
      duPont de Nemours
      Eliot, Dr. Ellsworth, Jr.
      Farnam, Henry W.
      Ford, George Hare
      Fuller, Luther
      Grenfell Fund
      Harriman, William Averell and Payne Whitney
      Hawley, George and Samuel
      Japanese Alumni of Yale
      Japan Society
      Judd, Albert F.
      McCay, Julia R.
      McKell, William
      Mansfield, Howard
      Miller, M. M.
      Modern Language Club
      North, J. Richard
      Read, Mrs. William A.
      Ridgeway, Gertrude Knight
      Ripley, A. L.
      Royal McKay Memorial
      Sanford Portrait Fund
      Seymour, George Dudley, re painting of John C. Calhoun
      Sherman, Roger, masonic apron of, gift of Henry Daggett Hooker
      Sherman, Roger, portrait of
      Shevlin Plaque
      Simpson, Louisa B.
      Taylor, William H.
      Tenney, John F.
      Tracy, Ernest B.
      Thompson, Robert M.
      Tyler, Victor M.
      Vanderbilt, Mrs. Cornelius
      Walker, Walter N.
      Warren, Samuel R.
      Wells, H. Gideon
      Whitney, Margaret D.
      Wilson, R. C.
      Wood, Mrs. Charles H.
      Yale Memorial Society Prize
      Miscellaneous correspondence
    - 240. Scientific School: expenditures, 1880s-1910 (Box 322, Folder 2068)
    - 242. Buildings, University, 1908-1930 (Box 322, Folder 2069)
    - 242a. Buildings, University: administration building, 1901 January-November (Box 322, Folder 2070)
    - 242b. Buildings, University: Woodbridge Hall, 1909 January-1916 November (Box 322, Folder 2071)
    - 243. Woolsey Hall: concerts, 1899, 1903, 1909-1922 (Box 322, Folder 2072-2073)
    - 243. Woolsey Hall: concerts, 1914-1932 (Box 323, Folder 2074)
    - 243a. Woolsey Hall: concerts--Cleveland Symphony Orchestra, Kneisel Quartet, Kreisler Concert, Albert Arnold Chamber Concerts, Whiting Recitals (1914-1923), 1914-1931 (Box 323, Folder 2075-2081)
    - 243a. Woolsey Hall: concerts -- Lorraine Wyman, 1916-1922 (Box 324, Folder 2082)
    - 243c. Woolsey Hall: concerts -- organ recitals, 1917-1924 (Box 324, Folder 2083)
    - 244. Divinity School, 1900, 1905-1930 (Box 324, Folder 2084-2085)
    - 244a. Theological Prizes, 1912 (Box 324, Folder 2086)
    - 245. Silliman Lectures, 1911-1916 (Box 324, Folder 2087)
    - 246. Wheeler (Albert S.): estate, 1905-1907 (Box 324, Folder 2088)
    - 247. Bicentennial Celebration, 1902, 1909 (Box 324, Folder 2089)
    - 248. Commercial Museum, Yale, 1905-1907 (Box 324, Folder 2090)
    - 249. Heating and Lighting Plant, 1906-1912 (Box 324, Folder 2091-2092)
    - 251. Blount or Sutton Land, 1908-1945 (Box 325, Folder 2093-2094)
    - 252. Honorary Degrees, 1906-1923 (Box 325, Folder 2095)
    - 254. Meacham Memorial, 1906 July-1907 November (Box 325, Folder 2096)
    - 255. Alumni Weekly, 1906 November-1916 April (Box 325, Folder 2097)
    - 256. Nathan Hale Statue, 1907 October-1913 July (Box 325, Folder 2098)
    - 257. Library Fund, 1907 November (Box 325, Folder 2099)
    - 260. Flags, 1907 November-1916 June (Box 325, Folder 2100)
    - 261. Miller (George Douglas), 1907-1921 (Box 325, Folder 2101-2102)
    - 261. Miller (George Douglas), 1910-1918 (Box 325A, Folder 2102a-d)
    - 263. Bureau of Appointments, 1907-1927 (Box 326, Folder 2103-2109)
    - 263. Bureau of Appointments, 1929-1931 (Box 327, Folder 2110-2111)
    - 264. Buildings and Maintenance: Department of Surgery, 1907 August-1908 April (Box 327, Folder 2112)
    - 265. Lampson Lyceum: engagements, 1913-1916 (Box 327, Folder 2113)
    - 266. Porter (John Addison) Prize, 1907 September-1916 April (Box 327, Folder 2114)
    - 267. Newberry Organ, 1915 July-1916 December (Box 327, Folder 2115)
    - 268. Real Estate: Litchfield County, Connecticut, 1908 March-1909 March (Box 327, Folder 2116)
    - 269. Funds:, 1912-1922 (Box 327, Folder 2117)
      Ayers (Edward Francis, Jr.) Memorial Fund
      Barnes (Henry Weldon) Memorial Fund
    - 269. Funds:, 1914-1924 (Box 328, Folder 2118-2222)
      Belgian Relief Fund
      Brady (Anthony N.) Memorial Foundation
      Brooke, Mrs. G. Clymer
      Brown, Thatcher M.
      Brown (William McKean) Memorial Publication Fund
      Chittenden Students" Fund
      Class Fund, 1911S
      Class Fund, 1912
      Classical Department Publication Fund
      Clement (S. Merrell) Publication Fund
      Cunningham (Oliver Baty) Memorial
      Mack (John) Memorial Fund
    - 269. Funds:, 1907-1913 (Box 329, Folder 2123-2124)
      Manice Fund
      University Chamber Music Endowment Fund
      Warren (Lewis Baker) Memorial Foundation
      Whiting Recital Fund
      Miscellaneous funds
    - 271. Connecticut Hall Fund, 1908 April (Box 329, Folder 2125)
    - 271a. Dormitories: McClellan Hall, 1924 August-1925 November (Box 329, Folder 2126)
    - 271b. Dormitories: Jonathan Edwards, 1924 December-1926 January (Box 329, Folder 2127)
    - 272. Grove Street Cemetery, 1908 April-1909 October (Box 329, Folder 2128)
    - 273. Yale Veterinary College, 1908 March (Box 329, Folder 2129)
    - 274. Real Estate: Litchfield County, Connecticut, 1905-1916 (Box 329, Folder 2130-2131)
    - 274. Real Estate: Litchfield County, Connecticut, 1907-1916 (Box 330, Folder 2132-2133)
    - 275. Photographs of Yale University: World'sFair, 1908 (Box 330, Folder 2134)
    - 276. Barnett, James F., 1908 April (Box 330, Folder 2135)
    - 278. Steinert Prize, 1908 June-1916 May (Box 330, Folder 2136)
    - 279. Yale Field, 1908-1924 (Box 330, Folder 2137)
    - 279a. Tompkins (Ray) Memorial: subscriptions, 1925 September-December (Box 330, Folder 2138)
    - 280. Yale Courant, 1906-1918 (Box 330, Folder 2139)
    - 281. Graduate School, 1908-1922 (Box 330, Folder 2140-2141)
    - 282a. Real Estate: Cincinnati, Ohio, 1909 June-1916 April (Box 330, Folder 2142)
    - 284. Visitors: American Bar Association Convention, 1908 August-September, 1916 September-1917 November (Box 331, Folder 2143)
    - 285. Real Estate: legal advice, 1908 June-September (Box 331, Folder 2144)
    - 285a. Real Estate: Washington State, 1911 April-November (Box 331, Folder 2145)
    - 286. Steinert Music Collection, 1908, 1913 (Box 331, Folder 2146)
    - 289. University Guides, 1908 May-1916 June (Box 331, Folder 2147)
    - 290. Writerpress, 1908 Oct, 1914 September-1915 March (Box 331, Folder 2148)
    - 291. Law School, 1908-1924 (Box 331, Folder 2149-2152)
    - 291a. Law School: insurance on library, 1911 January (Box 331, Folder 2153)
    - 291b. Law School: dormitory and Yale Law School Journal, 1917-1924 (Box 331, Folder 2154)
    - 291c. Law School: Alumni Association, 1921-1924 (Box 331, Folder 2155)
    - 291c. Law School: gifts, 1917-1920 (Box 331, Folder 2156)
    - 291c. Law School: Guarantee Fund, 1921-1928 (Box 331, Folder 2157)
    - 292. Plumbing Inspections, 1908-1909 (Box 331, Folder 2158)
    - 293. Accounting Methods, 1908 November-1913 February (Box 331, Folder 2159)
    - 293a. Vouchers, 1911 March (Box 331, Folder 2160)
    - 294. Vacuum Cleaners, 1908 October-1913 October (Box 332, Folder 2161)
    - 295. Surety Bonds, 1907 January-1922 June (Box 332, Folder 2162)
    - 296. Woolsey Bust, 1908 November-1909 February (Box 332, Folder 2163)
    - 298. Connecticut Cincinnati Funds, 1908 November (Box 332, Folder 2164)
    - 300. Memorials:
      - General correspondence, 1908-1923 (Box 332, Folder 2165)
      - Rhodes (Billy) and Welch (George A.), 1915 February-1916 December (Box 332, Folder 2166)
    - 302. Kit Kat Club, undated (Box 332, Folder 2167)
    - 303. Connecticut Educational Society, 1890-1910 (Box 332, Folder 2168)
    - 304. New England Lime Company, 1908-1909 (Box 332, Folder 2169)
    - 306. Medical School:
      - General correspondence, 1909-1914 (Box 332, Folder 2170)
      - General correspondence, 1915-1921 (Box 333, Folder 2171-2173)
      - General correspondence, 1922-1930 (Box 334, Folder 2174-2179)
      - Chinese paintings of tumors, 1914 March-1915 April (Box 334, Folder 2180)
      - Department of Obstetrics and Department of Public Health, 1915-1923 (Box 334, Folder 2181)
      - Department of University Health, 1916-1923 (Box 334, Folder 2182)
      - Financial statements of Winchester Repeating Arms Co., 1923 August-1926 December (Box 335, Folder 2183)
      - General Hospital Society of Connecticut and estate of Sarah T. Winchester, 1922-1926 (Box 335, Folder 2184)
      - Department of Physiology and Nathan Smith Hall, 1918 November-1923 November (Box 335, Folder 2185)
      - New Haven Hospital Building, 1923 July-1927 December (Box 335, Folder 2186-2189)
    - 307. Library Acquisitions: Louisville Municipal Reports, 1908 December-1909 March (Box 336, Folder 2190)
    - 309. Wright (Henry P.), 1909 February-March (Box 336, Folder 2191)
    - 310. Daniels Memorial Gateway, 1909 January-1914 August (Box 336, Folder 2192)
    - 311. University Avenue, 1909 May-1917 November (Box 336, Folder 2193)
    - 313. Music School, 1909 July-1928 December (Box 336, Folder 2194-2195)
    - 314. New Haven Educational Extension: public lecture course, 1910 April-1911 October (Box 336, Folder 2196)
    - 315. Wright (Henry P.) Fund, 1908 September-1911 January (Box 336, Folder 2197)
    - 316. Hudson-Fulton Celebration Exhibition, 1909 July (Box 336, Folder 2198)
    - 317. Mercer (Alexander G.) Estate, 1909 July-1910 January (Box 336, Folder 2199)
    - 318, Proctor, William: athletic tickets, 1909 June-1910 October (Box 336, Folder 2200)
    - 319. Night Watchman, 1909 May-June (Box 336, Folder 2201)
    - 320. Sanford, Foster: football, 1909 May-June (Box 336, Folder 2202)
    - 321. Adams Express Co., 1909-1919 (Box 336, Folder 2203)
    - 322. Chamber of Commerce Banquet, 1910-1913 (Box 336, Folder 2204)
    - 323. Betts Prize: Law School, 1906-1913 (Box 336, Folder 2205)
    - 324. Kellogg (Dr. C. W.) Claim, 1909 May-1912 May (Box 336, Folder 2206)
    - 325. Wright (Henry P.): retirement, 1909 June (Box 336, Folder 2207)
    - 327. Art School Building: addition, 1909 May-1911-May (Box 336, Folder 2208)
    - 327a. Art School: Pardee Publication Fund, Thomas Rutherford Trowbridge Memorial Lectureship Fund, John Davenport Wheeler, Architecture Scholarship, miscellaneous, 1911-1918 (Box 337, Folder 2209)
    - 328. Day Mission Library, 1909 September-1916 December (Box 337, Folder 2210-2212)
    - 328b. Day Mission Library: Clark Co. Contract, 1911-1912 (Box 337, Folder 2213)
    - 329. Forest School Library Fund, 1909 September (Box 337, Folder 2214)
    - 330. Dining Hall Register, 1909 September (Box 337, Folder 2215)
    - 331. Dormitory Telephones, 1909 October-1910 October (Box 337, Folder 2216)
    - 332. Class Ivies, 1909 July-1914 December (Box 337, Folder 2217)
    - 333. Gifts: prospective gifts to Yale University, 1909 October-1915 October (Box 337, Folder 2218)
    - 334. Insurance: portraits in University Dining Hall, 1909 October (Box 337, Folder 2219)
    - 335. Boocock Fund and Library, 1909 September-October (Box 337, Folder 2220)
    - 336. Keys, 1909 October-1916 October (Box 337, Folder 2221)
    - 337. Lost Checks, 1909 August-September (Box 337, Folder 2222)
    - 338. Birdseye (Clarence F.), The American College: college bookkeeping practices, 1909 September-October (Box 337, Folder 2223)
    - 339. Hemingway (Rev. Jacob): gravestone maintenance, 1909 June-1912 June (Box 337, Folder 2224)
    - 340. Mulliken (Harral): Business Administration, Graduate School, 1908 July (Box 337, Folder 2225)
    - 341. Mann (Arthur S.) Memorial Fund, 1909 June (Box 337, Folder 2226)
    - 342. Willcox (David) Loan Fund, 1909 June-1917 October (Box 337, Folder 2227)
    - 343. Engine House Site, 1909 June-1910 March (Box 337, Folder 2228)
    - 344. Athletic Association:
      - General correspondence, 1908 July-1915 March (Box 337, Folder 2229)
      - General correspondence, 1915 April-1928 December (Box 338, Folder 2230-2235)
      - Board of Control, 1915 November-1926 December (Box 339, Folder 2236-2237)
      - Boat house property, 1916 September (Box 339, Folder 2238)
      - Conduct memorandum, 1915 November (Box 339, Folder 2239)
      - Contributions for ground development, 1919 June-1922 June (Box 339, Folder 2240)
      - Distribution of Yale Bowl tickets, 1922 November-1930 December (Box 339, Folder 2241-2244)
      - Fund Statements, 1917 May-1920 March (Box 339, Folder 2245)